<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Challenge_1</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>

    <string name="egypt_details">Egypt, officially the Arab Republic of Egypt, is a transcontinental country spanning the
        northeast corner of Africa and southwest corner of Asia, via a land bridge formed by the Sinai Peninsula. It is the
        world\'s only contiguous Eurafrasian nation. Most of Egypt\'s territory of 1,010,408 square kilometres (390,000 sq mi)
        lies within the Nile Valley. Egypt is a Mediterranean country. It is bordered by the Gaza Strip and Israel to the northeast,
        the Gulf of Aqaba to the east, the Red Sea to the east and south, Sudan to the south and Libya to the west.</string>

    <string name="england_details">England is a country that is part of the United Kingdom. It shares land borders with Scotland
        to the north and Wales to the west. The Irish Sea lies northwest of England and the Celtic Sea lies to the southwest.
        England is separated from continental Europe by the North Sea to the east and the English Channel to the south.
        The country covers much of the central and southern part of the island of Great Britain, which lies in the North Atlantic;
        and includes over 100 smaller islands such as the Isles of Scilly, and the Isle of Wight.</string>

    <string name="france_details">France, officially the French Republic, is a sovereign state comprising territory in western Europe
        and several overseas regions and territories. The European part of France, called metropolitan France, extends from the
        Mediterranean Sea to the English Channel and the North Sea, and from the Rhine to the Atlantic Ocean. France spans 643,801 square
        kilometres (248,573 sq mi) and has a total population of 66.6 million. It is a unitary semi-presidential republic with
        the capital in Paris, the country\'s largest city and main cultural and commercial centre. The Constitution of France establishes
        the state as secular and democratic, with its sovereignty derived from the people.</string>

    <string name="germany_details">Germany, officially the Federal Republic of Germany is a federal parliamentary republic in West-Central Europe.
        It includes 16 constituent states and covers an area of 357,021 square kilometres (137,847 sq mi) with a largely temperate seasonal climate.
        Its capital and largest city is Berlin. With about 81.5 million inhabitants, Germany is the most populous member state in the European Union.
        After the United States, it is the second most popular migration destination in the world.</string>

    <string name="italy_details">Italy, officially the Italian Republic is a unitary parliamentary republic in Europe. Italy covers an area of
        301,338 km2 (116,347 sq mi) and has a largely temperate seasonal climate; due to its shape, it is often referred to in Italy as lo Stivale
        (the Boot). With 61 million inhabitants, it is the 4th most populous EU member state. Located in the heart of the Mediterranean Sea,
        Italy shares open land borders with France, Switzerland, Austria, Slovenia, San Marino and Vatican City.</string>

    <string name="netherlands_details">The Netherlands is the main "constituent country" of the Kingdom of the Netherlands. It is a small,
        densely populated country located in Western Europe with three island territories in the Caribbean. The European part of the Netherlands
        borders Germany to the east, Belgium to the south, and the North Sea to the northwest, sharing maritime borders with Belgium, the United
        Kingdom and Germany. The largest and most important cities in the Netherlands are Amsterdam, The Hague and Rotterdam. Amsterdam is the
        country\'s capital, while The Hague holds the Dutch seat of government and parliament. The port of Rotterdam is the largest port in
        Europe – as large as the next three largest combined – and was the world\'s largest port between 1962 and 2004. The name Holland is also
        frequently used to refer informally to the whole of the country of the Netherlands. I love this country the most.</string>

</resources>
